我将尝试另一种我以前从未尝试过的方式，例如，你可以做诗歌。
I'm going to try another way that I've never tried before, which is you could do maybe poetry, for example.
如果我能写诗，如果我能写文字，也许我能写歌。
If I can write verse, if I can write text, maybe I could write poetry.
我以前从未写诗。
I've never written poetry before.
我做得很糟糕。
I'm terrible at it.
也不是什么大粉丝。
Not a big fan, either.
但也许我们可以说，我想为我的妻子写一首漂亮的诗，作为我可以在她生日时送给她的一些聪明的东西，以及Chad GBT帮我找到的她那把凶残、苍白、苍白的刀或其他什么。
But maybe let's say I want to write a nice poem for my wife as something clever I can give her on her birthday along with her murderous, hoary, hoary knife that Chad GBT helped me to find or whatever.
所以，让我们在乍得GBT写一首诗，只是为了好玩，一些你可以做的有趣的事情。
So let's write a poem here in Chad GBT just for fun, some fun things you can do.
我可以说，写一首诗。
And I could just say, write a poem.
我妻子喜欢园艺，对吧？
and my wife likes gardening, right?
写一首关于园艺的诗，让我们来谈谈园艺的乐趣吧。
Write a poem about gardening, let's say about the joys of gardening.
园艺有乐趣吗？
Is there joys in gardening?
我不是园丁。
I'm not a gardener.
这看起来像是在拔草。
It seems like a lot of weed pulling.
但是园艺的乐趣，然后你可以放一些东西，比如艾米丽·迪金森的风格，对吧？
But joys of gardening, and then you could put in things like in the style of, let's say, of Emily Dickinson, right?
著名诗人。
The famous poet.
我只认识几个。
I only know a couple.
艾米莉·迪克森，迪克森。
Emily Dickson, Dickson.
好吧，好吧。
All right, okay.
现在，它将以多快的速度回来，讲述守护我们众多的快乐和真实的一块来自地球的露水，感受你指尖之间的土壤等等，花朵的香味，我的意思是这是一个我的意思
and now it's going to look how fast it is it's going to come back about the joys of guarding our many and true a piece that comes from the earth and the dew the feel the soil between your fingertips and so on right the scent of blooms i mean this is a i mean i
我会告诉她，因为我是一个诚实的人，我不会做不道德的事情。
I would tell her because I'm an honest person and I don't do unethical things.
但如果你不是一个诚实的人，你只想把这一切据为己有，然后说，哦，海伦，我可爱的妻子，我太爱你了。
But if you're not an honest person, you want to just take this all for your own and say, oh, Helen, my lovely wife, I love you so much.
我给你写了一首诗。
I wrote a poem for you.
这是关于园艺的。
And it's about gardening.
这是关于园艺的乐趣。
It's about the joys of gardening.
但ChatGPT没有抄袭艾米丽·迪金森的一首诗，这不是很疯狂吗。
But isn't it crazy where ChatGPT is not copying a poem from Emily Dickinson.
这不是拿艾米丽·迪金森和剽窃。
It's not taking Emily Dickinson and plagiarizing.
这是艾米丽·迪金森的风格。
It's in the style of Emily Dickinson.
这是关于园艺的，但不是
And it's about gardening, but it's not
她的实际工作，所以这不是抄袭或其他什么，这是一项由人工智能完成的独特工作，然后你在其中添加更多内容，使其真正独特，更人性化，对吧？
her actual work, so it's not plagiarism or anything, it is a unique piece of work done by artificial intelligence and then you add more to it to make it truly unique and more human than that, right?
所以，我们刚刚写了一首艾米丽·迪金森风格的诗，对吧？
So there, we just wrote a poem in the style of Emily Dickinson, right?
所以，为了好玩，我们想做同样的事情，因为我们现在正在进行聊天，我们可以在此基础上继续，我不必开始新的聊天或其他任何事情，我想用TS Elliot的风格说，是吗？
So let's say, for fun, let's say we want to do the same thing, because we have this chat now going on, we can just build on this, I don't have to start a new chat or anything, I'm gonna say in the style of, is it TS Elliot?
向你展示了我对诗歌的了解，对吧？
shows you what I know about poetry, right?
你知道，所以现在我们得到的快乐是巨大而深刻的。
You know, so now we got the joys are vast and profound.
所以现在我们要换一种方式，额头上的汗水，手上的污垢。
So now we're taking a different thing, the sweat on the brow, the dirt on your hands.
你可以看到风格是如何不同的，在风格上有点不同，你知道，无论是说什么，还是怎么说。
You see how the style is different, a little bit different in terms of style, you know, both what's being said, but also how it's being said.
所以，拿起你的工具，整理你的情节，找到买不到的快乐和简单的东西。
So take up your tools and tend your plot and find the joy and simple things that cannot be bought.
天哪。
Oh my goodness.
如果我做同样的事情，比方说，让我们再做一个沃尔特的惠特曼。
And if I do the same thing, let's say, let's do one more Walt's Whitman.
你们可以玩得开心。
and you guys can have your own fun with this.
这是一样的事情。
And it's the same thing.
看看它是如何的，它们是如何不同的，你可以重新生成它并尝试不同的事情。
See how it's, how they're different and you can regenerate this and try different things.
在那里，我刚刚写了三首关于园艺的诗，有三种不同的风格。
There, I just wrote three poems about gardening with three different styles.
我这辈子从来没有写过诗，它们不是，它们并不可怕，我的意思是这是园艺，但它还不错，我的目的是它还不错
and I've never written a poem before in my life and they're not they're not terrible it is I mean it is it is gardening but it's it's not bad I mean it's not bad you know and I maybe I could pull from these three add my unique stuff you know and you know um you know maybe I could say oh do I want to do this write a poem about gardening and the gardener is my wife and the gardener
让我们疯狂起来吧，我爱海伦，她的名字叫海伦，我可爱的加纳，我亲爱的加纳妻子，也是一名会计师，是的，海伦是一个老式的迷因，她不像106岁
let's get crazy is my love of Helen her name is Helen my lovely Garner my lovely Garner wife who's also an accountant and yes Helen is an older style meme she is not like 106 years old
见鬼，天哪。
Hell, oh my goodness.
地狱在我的爱中，园丁神圣，她的手在美丽的土壤中如此细腻。
Hell in my love, the gardener divine, her hand in the soil of beauty so fine.
哇！
Wow.
同样，你可以，对我们所有人来说，如果你是一名专业作家，如果你主修诗歌和所有这些，你可以看看这是否有好处。
Again, you can, for all our, if you're a professional writer, if you're a major in poetry and all this, you can take a look at this and you can see whether this is any good.
但是，天哪，如果我写了这篇文章，我的爱见鬼去吧，园丁是如此的真实，她对生活的热情，一种看得见的景象。
But boy, if I wrote this, hell in my love, the gardener so true, her passion for life, a sight to view.
天哪。
Oh my gosh.
她要么会喜欢它，要么在这一点上被抛弃。
She's either gonna love it or be thrown up at this point.
所以
So.
但我只是想展示一下你如何也能在GPT上玩得开心。
But I'm just trying to show how you can have fun with GPT too.
实际上，除了数据库之外，最大的限制，但最大的真正限制是你的想象力。
And really the limitation, the biggest limitation besides the database on it, but the biggest real limitation is your imagination.
如果你能想象为你的老妻子写一首诗，你一生的挚爱，她是一个园丁，在没有经验的情况下创作一首诗。
If you can imagine like writing a poem for your longtime wife, the love of your life, who is a gardener divide and create a poem with no experience.
我觉得这很酷，也许值得一看，也许也很有趣。
I think that's pretty cool and maybe worth a look and maybe have fun having fun with it too.
除了如何真正帮助你在工作中取得成功之外，这才是真正的关键。
In addition to how you can really help you be successful at work and that's the real key thing.
因此，除了在工作生活和个人生活中使用聊天GPT之外，还可以享受聊天GPT的乐趣。
So have fun with chat GPT as well in addition to using it in both your work life and your personal life.